<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Todd&#39;s Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Todd&#39;s Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:13:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Unit Testing in Visual Studio 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/post/2017/03/10/live-unit-testing-in-visual-studio-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:13:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/post/2017/03/10/live-unit-testing-in-visual-studio-2017/</guid>
      <description>I am a big proponent of unit testing my code because of the many benefits it provides:
 Helps me to catch potential bugs early Helps me to clarify the behavior of my units (classes) from a client perspective Leaves a documentation trail for those that come behind me to understand my intentions  The only irritation/friction I have found in the past is the fact that running unit tests has required me to manually run them on a periodic basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>TODD A. MEINERSHAGEN 1850 Countryside Dr., Frisco, TX 75034 Home 972.712.2771 • Cellular 972.343.8652 todd@meinershagen.net

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS
 Accomplished architect with 17+ years of in-depth, hands-on experience designing and developing service-oriented, n-tier applications to solve business problems. Diverse certifications  MCSD.NET Profession Scrum Master I MongoDB for Node.JS Developers and DBAs Certificate for Java Development  Team player with a consistent history of &amp;ldquo;Far Exceeds&amp;rdquo; rating for end of year reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.toddmeinershagen.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Todd Meinershagen Summary  Accomplished architect with 20+ years of in-depth, hands-on experience designing and developing service-oriented, n-tier applications to solve business problems.
 Love working with people, improving process, learning new technologies/techniques and generating ideas while striving for excellence in everything that I do.
 Teacher&amp;rsquo;s heart and a diligent passion to accomplish.
  Specialties  Agile Process Process Engineering In-depth Systems/Tools Knowledge Technology Architecture and Design  Experience Senior Software Architect</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>